Id;Default;en;de
DataLogManager_Desc;This is the toplevel instance for logging data.;This is the toplevel instance for logging data.;Toplevel Instanz für das Daten Logging.
DataLogHighTask_Desc;In this task comparison and creating entries is done.;In this task comparison and creating entries is done.;In dieser Task wird der Vergleich und das Anlegen von Einträgen durchgeführt.
DataLogLowTask_Desc;In this task writing to storage is done.;In this task writing to storage is done.;In dieser Task wird auf das Speichermedium geschrieben.
DataLogChannels_Role;Channels for DataLog;Channels for DataLog;Kanäle für das Logging
DataLogChannel_Desc;These modules sort the data log entries.;These modules sort the data log entries.;Diese Module werden zur Sortierung der Log-Einträge genutzt.
DataLogStorage_Role;A storage module.;A storage module.;Modul zur Speicherung.
Enable_Name;Enable;Enable;Aktivieren
Enable_Desc;FALSE: Variables stored by this channel are not logged.;FALSE: Variables stored by this channel are not logged.;FALSE: Variablen dieses Kanals werden nicht gelogged.
SaveInFirstCycle_Name;SaveInFirstCycle;Save in first cycle;Speichere im ersten Zyklus
SaveInFirstCycle_Desc;Log values of all variables used in this channel in first cycle of application.;Log values of all variables used in this channel in first cycle of application.;Logge die Werte aller Variablen dieses Kanals während des ersten Zyklus der Applikation.
storageName_Name;StorageName;Storage Name;Speicherung-Name
storageName_Desc;Name of the storage. Use $$CHANNEL_NAME$$ when using the name of the channel (parent).;Name of the storage. Use $$$$CHANNEL_NAME$$$$ when using the name of the channel (parent).;Name der Speicherung. Benutzen sie $$$$CHANNEL_NAME$$$$ um den Namen des Kanales (Vatermodul) zu verwenden
DataLogStorage_SQLite_Desc;Representing a SQLite storage.;Representing a SQLite storage.;Entspricht einer SQLite-Speicherung.
CsvStorage_Desc;Representing a CSV storage.;Representing a CSV storage.;Entspricht einer CSV-Speicherung.
Seperator_Name;Seperator;Seperator;Seperator
Seperator_Desc;The seperator used in CSV.;The seperator used in CSV.;Separator, der in CSV-Dateien verwendet wird.
bufferSize_Name;BufferSize;Buffer size;Puffergröße
bufferSize_Desc;Size of the internal buffer.;Size of the internal buffer.;Größe des internen Puffers.
bufferFillLevel_Name;BufferFillLevel;Buffer fill level;Puffer Füllstand
bufferFillLevel_Desc;The data is written only if the buffer is filled above this level in percent. 0 to deactivate.;The data is written only if the buffer is filled above this level in percent. 0 to deactivate.;Daten werden nur geschrieben, falls der Puffer einen Füllstand, entsprechend dieser Angabe in Prozent, erreicht hat. 0 deaktiviert die Pufferung.
SaveCyclic_Name;Save Cyclic;Save Cyclic;Zyklische Speicherung
SaveCyclic_Desc;Save all variables of this Channel cyclic in this interval. Set to T#0S to deactivate periodically logging.;Save all variables of this Channel cyclic in this interval. Set to T#0S to deactivate periodically logging.;Speichert alle Variablen dieses Kanals persiodisch, in Abständen dieses Intervals. T#0S deaktiviert dieses periodische Logging.
MaxEntries_Name;Number of entries;Maximal number of entries;Maximale Anzahl der Einträge
MaxEntries_Desc;The maximum number of entries allowed for the table belonging to this module instance. Set to 0 to deactivate.;The maximum number of entries allowed for the table belonging to this module instance. Set to 0 to deactivate.;Maximale Anzahl an Einträgen die für die Tabelle, die zu diesem Modul gehört, erlaubt ist. 0 deaktiviert die maximale Grenze.
CRCCheck_Name;CRC Check;CRC Check;CRC Überprüfung
CRCCheck_Desc;Enable CRC check when logging to ensure consitent log entries;Enable CRC check when logging to ensure consitent log entries.;Aktiviert eine CRC Überprüfung während des Loggings um die Konsistenz der geloggten Einträge zu sichern.
addSurroundingSignForStringEntries_Name;Add surroundings;Add surroundings;Füge umschließende Zeichen ein
addSurroundingSignForStringEntries_Desc;Whether to add surrounding signs for (W)STRING entries.;Whether to add surrounding signs for (W)STRING entries.;Sollen (W)STRING Einträge von diesen Zeichen umschlossen werden.
addSurroundingSignForStringEntries_Group;Surroundings;Surroundings;Umschließende Zeichen
surroundingSignForStringEntries_Name;Surrounding signs;Surrounding signs;Umschließendes Zeichen
surroundingSignForStringEntries_Desc;The signs that shall be used as surroundings.;The signs that shall be used as surroundings.;Die Zeichen, die für das Umschließen verwendet werden sollen.
;;;
